[{"answer": "Doing the Piers Morgan interview.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "ORGAN: What has been the single greatest moment of your life?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "You don't want to be old and 80 and facing death, do you?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Yes, but you've done a lot, that's the point.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "What's -- what -- what -- what shall transpire?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Made some of the biggest TV shows --", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Done what?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "That's pushing the universe, expanding the universe.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "Dark matter?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Because that could be the answer to the mystery of life.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Why do you need to know what dark matter is?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "I am intrigued.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "ORGAN: Do you ever want to find out the answer to the mystery of life?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "I'm in torment.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "Do you fear death?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "That this continues.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "What do you hope happens?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Piers, if you were given the opportunity to get a great interview, a great interview, but you're -- you're sick and you're tired and you're in your bed, wouldn't you get up out of bed --", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Why do you still put yourself through this?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm going to do that record.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "Is that how you feel, the same way?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "You might -- you might be able to relax.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "What will happen if I don't?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "Spend more time with your horses.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Relax and do what?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "Is it?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "I look 60?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "I like making people laugh.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "What is the one thing, if you're completely honest, that you enjoy above everything else that you've ever done?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "I -- I wish I -- well, I do a form of it with enough good material.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Do you like stand-up comedy?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Well, I -- I am, basically, in the one man show called \"How Time Flies.\"", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "If comedy is the thing that really gets you going, do you not fancy taking the ultimate risk, and going on a stand-up tour?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "My mother was an exuberant, silly lady.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "What did she teach you about life?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "I'm such -- I'm terrible at the jokes.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Shatner joke, yes?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "Oh, the roast was -- oh, well, it was actor George Takei was given the line that was the line.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "What was the one from your roast that you found most offensive and yet funny?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "No, I didn't.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Why didn't you go to the conventions?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "I should have done.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "Why didn't you?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "I would have done.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Why didn't you?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "I just don't think they ever had one in my neck of the woods, a little sleepy village in the east -- in the south of England.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "Why didn't you?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "And Captain Kirk was like my idol.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "You know why?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "It's part of the myth.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Joseph Campbell.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "What is the myth?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "No, I'm not sick of it.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Are you absolutely sick of it?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "No, really.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "It disappears.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "Is it, do you think?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Do you not worry about your legacy?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Not really, although we had heard rumors that the Southern stations, some Southern stations might -- might cut it down.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "Did you realize at that moment how significant that was going to be?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "I -- as far as I'm concerned.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "Is that all it's about, really?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "But when in doubt, whack Captain Kirk?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "They didn't have great scenes.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "He nicked my best lines?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "I care that somebody in this world dislikes me.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Do you care?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "He doesn't know me very well.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "How has Leonard managed to avoid despising you?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Are you good friends with him?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "Going crazy.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Going crazy?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "My mother ate cake.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Do you have an opening line?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "-- disciples what they want?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "\"Beam me up, Scotty.\"", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "What would you like to know?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "I had built up -- I thought it was derision.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "Well, do you have an ex-wife?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "I have.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Have you been like that in your life, would you say?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Some shame.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "Unashamedly so?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "How much?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "They're hormonal, Piers.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "What have you learned about women?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Well, not at that moment.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Have you ever said to a woman, you're being hormonal, and it's made it better?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "But does your wife, Elizabeth, go along with this theory?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "She's understanding.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "I don't know whether it's the type of woman I needed to be with.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "What have you learned about you through this whole process, about the type of woman you needed to be with?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "No, there isn't.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "But there is, isn't there?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "HATNER: No.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "You don't think so?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "-- an anathema.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "You don't have a day off sick?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "No, I've never been sick.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "A day off sick?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "I've never had an understudy.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "Always turned up?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "It's Latin, right, no.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "You can't even say it, can you?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "You're a Tweeter, aren't you, William?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, it's extraordinary.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "What do you make of the social networking phenomena?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Is one of the downsides of Twitter, Facebook, and so on that famous people just give way too much of themselves, that they kind of kill the magic?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Doing a Piers Morgan interview.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "What would you -- what would you choose?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "Well, of course.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "Can you replicate that?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "There are -- Piers.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "What's been the greatest professional moment?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "Is that what it's all about?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "And do you live for those moments?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "Do you believe that?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "I don't know what they're going to do.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "What are you going to do?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "Well, it's totally -- it's fraught with terrible decisions.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "But if you could, how are you seeing it all unraveling now?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "HATNER: Oh, no, no, no, no.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "Do you think you're a good singer or you're an entertainer?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 696, "question": "Does it ever stray into singing, do you think?", "qSentId": 695}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "Is it an early form of rap?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "I'm going to go next door.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 722, "question": "Where do you want to boldly go to next?", "qSentId": 721}, {"answer": "It could have been.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 734, "question": "That decision, was that the greatest decision you've ever taken?", "qSentId": 733}, {"answer": "I thought, I'm rich, I'm beyond -- beyond any concept of being rich.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "But when you watched the stock going up, what were you thinking?", "qSentId": 741}, {"answer": "It was the only intelligent decision to make.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 771, "question": "Was your decision to sell your stock, when it bottomed out, the worst decision of your life?", "qSentId": 770}, {"answer": "A few.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 774, "question": "Well, what happened -- can you think of another dot-com company that exists?", "qSentId": 773}, {"answer": "You've got to buy my record, and a few books, and the DVD.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 781, "question": "So, all this sort of impression that you're this billionaire, actually, you need to sell a few records, don't you?", "qSentId": 780}, {"answer": "And come in Canada when I do the one-man show.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 783, "question": "Anything else?", "qSentId": 782}, {"answer": "Get out of here.", "docId": "111120pmt", "aSentId": 794, "question": "Shall we just beam ourselves out of here?", "qSentId": 793}]